<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
	<record id="google_drive.view_google_drive_config_form" model="ir.ui.view">
	    <field name="arch" type="xml">
	        <form string="Google Drive Configuration">
	            <field name="model" invisible="1" />
	            <group>
	                <field name="name" />
	                <field name="active" widget="boolean_toggle"/>
	                <field name="model_id"/>
	                <label for='filter_id' />
	                <div>
	                    <field name='filter_id' />
	                    <p class="oe_grey">
	                        <b>To create a new filter:</b><br/>
	                        - Go to the Viindoo document you want to filter. For instance, go to Opportunities and search on Sales Department.<br/>
	                        - In this "Search" view, select the option "Save Current Filter", enter the name (Ex: Sales Department)<br/>
	                        - If you select "Share with all users", link of google document in "More" options will appear for all users in opportunities of Sales Department.<br/>
	                        - If you don't select "Share with all users", link of google document in "More" options will not appear for other users in opportunities of Sales Department.<br/>
	                        - If filter is not specified, link of google document will appear in "More" option for all users for all opportunities.
	                    </p>
	                </div>
	                <field name='google_drive_template_url' placeholder="https://viindoo.com/documentation/15.0/applications/getting-started/external-apps-integration/google-drive-intergration.html#steps-to-use-the-google-drive-integration-feature-in-viindoo" required="1" />
	                <field name='google_drive_resource_id' invisible="1" />
	                <label for='name_template' />
	                <div>
	                    <field name='name_template' />
	                    <p class="oe_grey">
	                        The name of the attached document can use fixed or variable data. To distinguish between documents in
	                        Google Drive, use fixed words and fields. For instance, in the example above, if you wrote Deco_Addict_%%(name)s_Sales
	                        in the Google Drive name field, the document in your Google Drive and in Viindoo attachment will be named
	                        'Deco_Addict_SO0001_Sales'.
	                    </p>
	                </div>
	            </group>
	        </form>
	    </field>
	</record>

	<record id='google_drive.action_google_drive_users_config' model='ir.actions.act_window'>
	    <field name="help" type="html">
	        <p class="o_view_nocontent_smiling_face">
	            Add a new template
	        </p>
	        <p>
	            Link your own google drive templates to any record of Viindoo. If you have really specific documents you want your collaborator fill in, e.g. Use a spreadsheet to control the quality of your product or review the delivery checklist for each order in a foreign country, ... Its very easy to manage them, link them to Viindoo and use them to collaborate with your employees.
	        </p>
	    </field>
	</record>

</odoo>
